<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bhaskar Vamsi ka Personal Blog</title>
    <link>https://dbvamsi.github.io/resume/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bhaskar Vamsi ka Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dbvamsi.github.io/resume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dbvamsi.github.io/resume/cv/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dbvamsi.github.io/resume/cv/resume/</guid>
      <description>Resume Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Page: / </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dbvamsi.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dbvamsi.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Bhaskar Vamsi Dontaraju&amp;rsquo;s current Resume Bhaskar Vamsi Dontaraju Technical Writer Loyalty, Commitment, and Discipline are integral to my character. I am a highly motivated information developer with good expertise and hands-on experience across structured authoring tools, API reference writing, UX writing, style guides, and Document Development Processes. Work Experience From To Where As what Feb 2022 Present epay gmbh - Munich, Germany Technical Writer Oct 2021 Jan 2022 Salesforce - Hyderabad, India Technical Writer Dec 2019 Oct 2021 Honeywell Technology Solutions - Hyderabad, India Exp Tech Writer April 2018 Nov 2019 Tech Mahindra Pvt Ltd - Hyderabad, India Technical Analyst Sep 2016 Apr 2018 Apex CoVantage India Limited - Hyderabad, India Technical Writer Aug 2014 Sep 2016 CAMP Systems Pvt Ltd - Hyderabad, India Associate Technical Writer Skills Acquired Microsoft Word MarkDown Proof reading JIRA/Confluence Microsoft Powerpoint YAML DITA XML JSON Microsoft Excel Technical writing API Reference Writing HTML Adobe FrameMaker Document Management System SnagIt Familiarity of JavaScript RoboHelp Document Development Life Cycle Agile Methodologies Product Development Life Cycle GIT (GitHub) Software Development Life Cycle Familiarity of Windows and Ubuntu Content Management Madcap Flare Information Architecture Familiarity of RestAPIs Familiarity of Software as a Service (SaaS) Education B.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
